After finishing the pose, you can open the pose file.
As the pose changes, the outfit wear effect is also gradually changed.
If there is a hole in the finger part, drag the plate.
Now let's make the effect of the cloth wrapping the body.
First, freeze the white outer plate.
Show the X-ray intersection.
Select the X-ray intersection.
Select the center of the model, then press Shift X to return to the normal display state.
In the form of fire simulation, drag the axis of the positioning ball to make the model rotate.
As the model rotates gradually, the skirt fixed at the edge will gradually wrap the model.
After adjusting, reduce the particle diameter to make the skirt fold more smoothly.
At the same time, reduce the conflict thickness to make the skirt wrap closer.
Remove the excess inner line and straight line points.
After adjusting, activate the frozen skirt edge.
Since the skirt was fixed by the frozen edge, it is open.
So after loosening the edge, the model will tighten because of the inertia.
This will have the effect of rolling up.
Activate the two edges and start modeling.
You can see that as the skirt is tightened and the edge of the leather fabric is added, there will be a wave-like effect.
Compare the effect is still relatively obvious.
After use, you can delete the edge that needs to be used to control.
After using, you can delete the edge that needs to be used to control.
You can delete the edge that needs to be used to control.
After Hoping, tap the velcro to hold the edge to rotate the model.
You can also turn it around and rotate the model is still not moving.
Crush two frozen skirt edges on the 2D window.
After crushing, an horizontal center 3D alignment ball will appear in the 3D window.
Then rotate these two plates in the horizontal direction and slightly adjust and turn on ability to modify the application.
You must use small complain to modify every little bit.
When the adjustment is relatively large, you must pay attention to adjust the group board, stabilize it, and then proceed to the next step.
And when rotating, you must select two plates in the 2D window at the same time to make the center of rotation close.
In the adjustment process, you can rotate to other angles to see if there is a problem with penetration.
After the adjustment is completed, it is the same as the previous method, and the benefit of this method is that the model does not need to turn anymore, and does not need to rotate to the front at the end.
Finally, you can prepare to merge the front.
First, separate the two points on the side, otherwise the line on the front cannot be merged.
A prompt will pop up that the line cannot be merged.
Do the same operation in the front.
Then merge these two lines.
After merging, there is no trace of the cross-sectional line in the front.
Next, process the edge of the flower.
In order to run faster, freeze the other plates first.
Activate two flower edge plates, and reduce the example interval to 5.
If there are no more details in the way of fold, you can reduce it to 3 again, and modify it.
Next, alter the wear some bit.
If there are no more details in the way of fold, you can adjust it anew.
Finally, make some adjustments to the clothes details.
First of all, the sleeves can be applied to a more voluminous fabric.
I chose the snow-covered fabric, which is relatively low in number and is more voluminous.
After opening the simulation, the sleeves will gradually become softer.
After finishing the overall clothing, it is necessary to hide the outer layers to check if the inner layers are penetrated by the model.
Because there may be penetration problems when the layers have been frozen before.
You can freeze the inner layers separately when the other layers are frozen.
This can keep the inner layers stable without affecting the other layers.
Next, let's make a pearl necklace.
Please download the pearl necklace name line in the demo.
Then open this file in the name line.
Then use the modern name line tool to add a name line along the outline of the board.
Due to the addition of a fixed stitch stretch in the board, the grid is deformed.
Therefore, the name line attached to the top has also deformed.
After removing the fixed stitch, simulate again to simulate the natural shape of the board.
You can see that the deformation problem has improved.
Finally, reduce the transparency of the fabric to 0 and only keep the name line.
Please note.
Due to the name line, there is no UV.
Therefore, do not hook a unified UV diagram when drawing.